[Music]
watch
what you call a Joe cell as such if you
call it that I didn't call it that other
people have but the Jo cell with
cons round rings that thing has been
built off the universe and the planet no
I didn't do it in the first place that
way I found out it lines up 100% to
exactly that CU I can draw your um atom
and I can draw your planets around the
sun on a piece of paper as they are and
just put a couple of lines on those and
you end up with a J so the Joe cell is
the name given to a special type of
hydrogen fuel cell this fuel cell is
said to allow any combustion engine on
the planet to run on
water 92 we we bought a V8 Rover from
the recers the petrol at that stage was
42 cents a lit government always tells
the truth um they said the petrol never
ever exceed 42 cents a l one week later
after we had the car on the road it had
hit 53 and Rising quickly I just went
grabbed the stainless steel from the
scrapyards threw it all together into
some weird order I don't even know why
how is it on a Friday afternoon which
was my son's birthday the 9th of October
I Threw It On a car this was on the
Rover this cell now I didn't hook it up
to the carburetor to the intake I don't
even know why I put it where I put it
but it ended up going uh hooking up
plain straight water through these
neutral plates onto heat
exchange on the 79 River SD 13500 not
fuel injected just carburetor
disconnected all the fuel lines all the
fuel everything else disconnected them
not left them on pulled them all off
hit the key damn thing
run the Jo cell is claimed to fun in
something like this it starts with the
water tap water goes into a conditioning
tub a series of magnetic plates with
electrical current negatively charged
the water over a period of hours this
negatively charged water goes into the
cell to tune it in electric current is
applied for a short period inside the
cell stainless tubes which are
positioned in strict relation to the
golden mean ratio receive an oscillating
DC current by tweaking this combination
frequency is created that allows the
water to break into its two parts easily
the hydrogen is fed directly into the
carburetor replacing the P if it works
the Joe cell is a standalone onboard
energy device it's claimed to get about
100 km per
cup the whole idea behind hydrogen fuels
is basically a version of that but the
fact is that it takes a lot of energy to
separate oxygen and hydrogen in order to
break up water molecules you need to put
in a lot of energy to break the bonds so
that when you burn hydrogen again it
liberates a lot of energy and becomes
water
again you got the T there we put the C
together and put it on his uh Rover and
L and behold it continued to running
after we turn the the fuel off so we
looked at each other and said R where's
the cada camera just couldn't be this
simple get with the Jo cell that's
coming to you with the electropuls and
hydrogen power that will blow your
engine away get on the frequency Groove
and plug your Caboose into the energy
that's loose with the total overunity
Tower Power
um I'd never seen I'd never done a day
science I don't know anything about
hydrogen oxygen gas as such don't know
about your brown anybody like that never
knew anything about anything as
such and I do know a hell of a lot about
mechanics you know pretty good Wiz on
that this balloon's going to do one of
three
things one is it's going to implode and
and Flame and turn the balloon inside
out and in rushing air is going to take
every hair off me or everything else the
second thing that's if we got the
implosive gas straight off just for
fun we got these bubbles will trickle
over down
here here on
[Music]
[Applause]
there yellow a bon
fragmented and we've got a frequency in
it which is hydrogen that's a low ne
negative way this is power
on this is dead straight PL
[Music]
water overunity devices are sometimes
called free energy devices and we say
that is a an inappropriate use of
language because clearly the electric
inertia that comes from the gravity
field due to fractality is not free and
there's a price to be paid in the case
of specifically hydrogen implosion
devices the inertia that's in the
hydrogen was put there by the Sun and
and that there took some work to do
[Music]
that if you have that above the water in
that
cell uh she will only suck up any water
or splashes to that okay but there's a
different thing happens if you put
charge to that we disconnected all the
means of petrol getting into the
carburetor there's no petrol getting the
carburetor there's no return carb to the
tank that was disconnected we run it
completely BL we purge the bowl of the
carburetor with negatively charged water
we actually poured water into the flock
chamber of the carbur yeah and cleaned
it out we try we give it a long long
time to really clean it out make sure it
wouldn't fire
pum pum pum
pum and then we got the cell Conn me
tell me what happens if you the
timing well what's the difference
between my water and your water it's
charged go and get your water you
planted the foot you lost B your best
water
mate what luri
that's what I got he said it was wrong
works it charge in the opposite damn
Direction because all you see the
positive is on the inside now but what
I'm saying is this cable supposed to be
up here this is best
little it's change the frequency in that
block and it's firing and yet there is
it's it's def why is all logic because
the water there's no water there's no
hydrogen there's no Oxygen going in it
is creating another form of
energy that is can't be explained
scientifically as we know science okay
that normally Ur 180° and they still
F put the spark plugs back to Sun and
you still run on the G
[Music]
I don't want touching all right does
that make sense we in neutral
yeah Joe is very sincere he's very
mechanically intuitive he's not educated
in a formal sense but he has uh evolved
his mechanical intuitions from his
perspective he's assembling what he
calls an octahedral magnetic field which
I would call phase conjugate so the
opposing conic approaches of magnetic
flux lines creates a kind of conic
Center what I call phase conjugate or
implosive so I have been teaching about
how capacitors can phase conjugate for
example how an egg makes life he has
done that magnetically
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
so the laws of energy conservation in
combination with the laws of
thermodynamics tell us that the you
can't get more energy out of a system
then originally went into it and
that's why these things just can't work
it really doesn't make sense to me that
the stuff could work if you think about
the water powered car for example if you
splitting hydrogen and oxygen burning it
and getting water out the other end you
could make a closed loop where the water
comes back into the system and if you're
getting more energy art than you put in
the thing will just run forever once you
get it started everything we know about
the universe and which is what science
is about trying to understand the way
the universe works the way the world
Works everything that we know tells us
that this is
possible some of the guys who'd seen the
car running think oh I I think Joe must
have put some Petrol in there he might
have had some he may have switched
bottles put another bottle in and I said
but we passed that bottle around and
took a drink out of it it was just water
in it suffering from a kind of delusion
refusing to accept reality with extreme
magnetic implosion he's actually able to
make the impurities in the water
vaporize in a magnetic Vortex I believe
that does relate to the the use of the
Joe cell classically for hydrogen in
that the concentric rings of the metal
cylinder that were used he actually
would identify which end of the metal
pipe was extruded first in the process
of manufacturer because there' be a
little bit of ion bias in the direction
of magnetic line up and down that metal
piece of pipe and if you balance those
perfectly end to end the concentric
pipes you create a perfectly what's
called phase conjugate or what he calls
octahedral magnetic fields love to uh to
have a device like that in my backyard
you know I wouldn't have to pay for
energy ever again but uh it's not going
to happen I never could understand why
if we had the possibility of having free
energy why we had to have energy we paid
for but that's capitalism and the uh
where our um Consciousness is at the
moment with our original group that we
formed which was called Astro
alternative scientific and technological
research organization and so we formed
this in the early 90s and um our aim was
to research a lot of the new energy that
was coming out at the moment and U Brown
um was a Bulgarian inventor who decided
to come to Australia after the war
started a factory in Sydney and he
started in um putting together uh
hydrogen gas generators and selling them
as a welding apparatus so we bought his
first hydrogen gas generator and
actually had to sign a statement that we
wouldn't use it for anything other than
um welding purposes although we wanted
to use it to run internal combustion
Motors then we decid to make up our own
fuel cell producing hydrogen on demand
got quite a bit higher uh fuel
efficiency and it even got to the point
where one night driving back from uh
casino to tabulam this uh hold and
station wagon a six-cylinder actually
ran out of petrol what we were doing is
we were supplementing the hydrogen
oxygen we were getting from the fuel
cell with the petrol and this actually
ran out of petrol and coughed and
sputtered and then continued running and
when we got home we found that the bowl
of petrol was completely empty and it
had been running just on the fuel cell
so that was quite exciting that we'
gotten 100% um efficiency out of this
fairly crude uh fuel
cell what happened after that
was we started telling friends about it
and they started to have some success
everyone started talking and it it
seemed to get everyone was getting
exciting about these fuel
[Music]
cells do
so we got anyone got
aess back in the morning I get a bang on
the door it comes out me dressing again
here's Professor Ron Davis who
apparently read up all the signs for
your brown on Brown's gas hydrogen and
oxygen gas and he's fronted at me
doorstep and he's driven from Sydney all
night long I'm you know I'm Professor on
Davis I said you know hydrogen oxygen
gas you're brown Brown's gas I said
uh-uh sorry and um don't know what
you're talking about he said oh oh
Anyway by the way he said I heard that
you got a car running off water yeah
well whatever yeah I did yeah he said
could I have a look at it I said sure So
went out the back and everything else
and and so on he's supposed to know all
this stuff so here's this big long
cylinder you can see plain water up into
it's got a glass in and everything else
and so we just we hooked it up to the
car hit the key he checked everything
that had no fuel and everything else um
so um fired it up and that surprised him
said you know what's in the tank nothing
you know there's no lines connected
right we go for
[Music]
drive so what we're doing too mate we're
pushing 7,000 revs instantly straight
out without any hesitation we're pushing
all of us yeah the yeah three of us in
the car
right we're pushing 7,000 revs out in
flam in third gear we weren't able to do
that before we even took one up to the
niman Aquarius Festival the 25th
anniversary and showed this Holden
station wagon with a fuel cell in it and
to my surprise quite a few people got
angry because they said why should you
be able to ride around with this fuel
cell and we still have to use petrol
from a Ser station but a couple of the
guys up there said oh your fuel cell is
a lot more efficient than
ours you know you're not bail bouncing
you're not losing out you
just then what's he do he wants to steal
the car other fell wants to take the
cell fellas come everywhere from then on
you know just
everywhere people come to me and say oh
yeah you know you got a for nothing
give it to the world I said okay I'll
give it to you is that right you want me
to give it to you are you going to give
it to the next
person it's plain water straight out of
a creek off a hill it has a neutral
plates it has positive outside negative
underneath as we see I now turn on a
battery charger
and you will see Hallelujah now look
down the side work your way over the
side you'll see the that's hydrogen
going downwards it won't break the
surface you see this Vapor coming off
the top that's possibly what's running
the cars whoever the guy is Joe never
put one side up never rode any single
thing never gave one person any
permission any time ever to write
anything about him I didn't do for Mak a
money off never charged anybody for any
of it yet Barry Hilton Ian hen still
selling things now on me for years wrote
books on me and every got the
information
[Music]
wrong the Jo cell as used by its creator
takes quite a tangent from logic rather
than feeding the hydrogen into the
carburetor the pipe is stoed at the end
and inserted into a piece of plastic
tube the engine is tuned into the Joe
cell frequency allowing it to run on a
universal power some called Zero Point
Energy however the scientific Community
call it Pure Fantasy and never the twine
shall
meet what we're doing is sitting up a a
frequency generator this thing here
seems to output something what Tunes in
the vehicle and makes it
run the car that runs on water is not
actually running on water no it's
running on an energy created by the
water that's the way I see it they don't
use
water can't possibly be running water
cuz the outlet from the cell is
connected to a dead
end I didn't understand why the vehicle
seemed to start and run perfectly when
nobody else seems to be able to hit it
this stuff works very
strangely so I just went on and did
different cars probably 20 to 30 cars
learned more information about things
built plates and cells and everything
else no electrolyte no power input
different placeat what shouldn't be
connected we get electricity off the
cells we get implosion explosion we get
all these different gases we ended up
getting a resonating feel within the
tubes so we actually have tubes in place
that aren't electrically connected but
are within the electrical field
producing gas so we've got excitement
happening they're just playing with
little
um just half truths making things sound
like they're possible because they have
all the elements of something that's
possible but the quantities are wrong
what what happened with the RTA was to
get the hydrogen fuel cell approved by
them they wanted to have a couple of
cells in new cars that they could test
crash it was going to cost around a quar
of a million dollars which we didn't
have a local member uh told a local
politician and so it actually got back
to the federal government at the time
they offered us
$110,000 and a new car if we would sign
over the rights to this fuel cell we
didn't think that was a good enough deal
because we wanted to hold some sort of
um proprietary rights over it so we
didn't do that and soon after that we
had a group called Asus uh saying it was
not in our best interest to continue
this line of research they stress their
point quite
vigorously even to the point where the
local police said that they didn't want
any fatalities in their district and
they gave us uh sought off shotguns to
protect ourselves with
so we knew it was serious when the
police were giving us arms to protect
ourselves had the Department of Defense
uh through H division were as standard
at what we were doing we showed them
through the workshop over the back of
Joe's Place we there for 3 Days
filming I think they were amazed that we
were just freely giving it away that we
weren't selling it the engineer from
Audi come across with a AO government
follow what we know definitely is Asia
Australian as Government they front up
on to see about themselves and
everything else um so on like that spun
him out in a couple of minutes too you
know we've had um Professor Ron Davis
wanting to take out these cars he took
the first one we never got a back or
anything else mechanics Engineers
physicists government people government
people following you everywhere bugging
you threatening you beyond 2000 we're
going to do articles on me and
everything else and then we get calls
somebody must have been bugging
somewhere and kind of sending me kids
back in the post to me if I go here be
the story so I said stuff is shut it
down not interested then they try and
come and take your
cars Stan Meyer um we first heard about
him um in the early 90s he had a uh
Volkswagen dune buggy operating on a
fuel cell 100%
efficiency so I went over to visit him
and see his uh Factory in Columbus Ohio
he not only had um cars and buses
running on this fuel cell he actually
had a commander 13 seat jet the Stan
Meyer said he wasn't too afraid of the
poers it be and he was going to go ahead
and develop his fuel cells anyway
especially since he had discovered the
frequency which would split water easily
um but unfortunately he was eating in a
restaurant he got up he said I've been
poisoned he walked outside he killed
over and he died within two years we had
lost three major inventors we lost Bruce
DePalma we lost Stanley Meyer and we
lost Ule Brown so even to this
day this fuel cell research uh is
not uh strictly legal and not allowed to
come out my challenge to people who say
they can do this sort of thing is bring
it along to University and show it off
to the professors of physics and
engineering and so on demonstrated to a
skeptical Audience Show us it can
actually work there's going to be a
whole bunch of Nobel prizes for showing
all the stuff can actually work I for
one be really fascinated to to see you
know just about everything we know about
physics being overturned so bring it on
we could run almost all of our internal
combustion and directly on implosive
hydrogen rather quickly easily and
directly so the lessons here are good
and civilization might even make it if
we could teach the principle and for
someone who has seen this and still
believes there might be some sort of uh
trick
involved maybe their Consciousness is
not ready to accept this not interested
in making the dollar not interested in
the business not interested in the fame
and Glory whatsoever at all don't want
to go down like they said in history as
a famous guy this this time it's like
Thomas you know putting his finger into
Jesus you know into the wound you know
he sees it he knows Jesus died on the
cross but he still doesn't believe it
until he puts his finger in there don't
want to go down the ground don't want to
go down history don't want to be known a
simple D you
[Music]
All You Need Is Love